

Contact

Phone

+63995 355 7320

Email

akiralamagna@gmail.com

Address

Caloocan, Philippines 1400

Programming Laguange

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- LIQUID
- RUBY

Project Management Tools

- JIRA
- Slack
- ClickUp
- Hubspot
- Trello
- Basecamp

Professional Tools

- Shopify
- Canva
- Shopify Plus
- Google Suite
- Pagefly
- Office Tools
- Gempages
- Adobe Photoshop
- Shogun
- Adobe Lightroom
- Webflow
- Webliow
- Github
- Plasmic
- Postman
- Figma
- Visual Studio

Akira Gil Lamagna

Shopify Developer

Seasoned and independent Shopify Developer with more than 3 years of experience in blending the art of design with the skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging.

Experience

Jul 2022 - Present

OpenStore Miami US

Shopify Technical Assistant

- Serves as Shopify all-around Developer.
- Debug and provide fixes for store bugs and issues.
- Set up marketing campaigns using announcements, banners, and discounts
- Migrate existing Shopify Stores to latest, fast and converting Shopify Themes
- Create and debug scripts for second-level applications like discount, shipping, and payment

🖕 Aug 2019 - Jul 2022

Clients from the Philippines, United States and Australia

Freelance Shopify Developer

- Create, build and manage Shopify stores for clients, businesses and companies
- Deliver engaging user experience through optimization of images, cross-browser

compatibility

- Expand features, refine code, and improve processes, producing smoother operations and enhancing user engagement
- Designed dynamic and browser compatible pages using Shopify page builder or other page building apps like Pagebuilder by Pagefly

Jun 2016 - Jul 19

Teleperformance Fairview

Technical Support Representitive

- Communicate with clients via phone calls to provide step-by-step solutions effective in resolving hardware or software problems
- Providing responses and solutions to issues experienced by users of technological products or services
- Serve as the first point of contact for customers with complaints or questions concerning company technological products/services

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

STI College, Fairview, Quezon City

Jun 2015 - Mar 2016 3rd Year - Undergraduate